What was it like for you, for those
who may be experiencing that now,
discovering that your child was autistic?
By the time he was diagnosed,
I was already aware
something was wrong.
So it was me begging
for a written diagnosis
in order for me to access
early intervention.
I had to beg for a written diagnosis.
Because by the time he was two,
I'm like, my son should be talking.
I had three other kids before him.
And his doctor was like,
"Just wait it out."
"Every kid is different."
But I still felt
something wasn't right.
So I started on my own
putting him in speech therapy
and things that I would look up to see
if that is what's wrong with my son,
what should I do?
Speech therapy, occupational therapy.
But in that time I was told
about the regional center,
which is where we in California go
to access supports and services
for our children
and young adults on the spectrum
and with disabilities.
And in order to access
the early intervention,
I needed to have a diagnosis
before he was three years old.